prepsportswear.com 2019-12-12

# High School Apparel, College Fan Gear, Pro Sports Clothing, and Custom Team Gear

This notice describes our privacy policy. Prep Sportswear knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we will attempt to do so carefully and sensibly. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect, how we use that information, and the choices we offer, including how to access and update information. **By visiting[www.PrepSportswear.com](http://www.prepsportswear.com/) (the “Site”), you are expressly accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy**. For other terms and conditions that apply to your use of this Site, please review our [Terms of Use](https://www.prepsportswear.com/site/company/termsofuse).

### What Personal Information Does Prep Sportswear Gather?

##### Information You Give Us

We receive and store any information you enter on our Site or give us in any other way. You provide information to Prep Sportswear when you register, sign in, manage your accounts, search for a page or product, place a product order, return an item, send us an e-mail, comments or other material, participate in a survey, contest, questionnaire or gift registry, or communicate with customer service. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and telephone number; gender; credit card information; e mail address; school or college affiliations; class year; or contact information of people to whom purchases have been shipped (for example, a gift recipient). When you share information publicly, whether with Prep Sportswear or others, it may be indexable by search engines.

##### Information Automatically Collected

We automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with Prep Sportswear. Like many websites, we use “cookies” that may uniquely identify your browser or account, and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our Site or other content served by or on behalf of our Site on other websites. Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, browser language, version and time zone setting, hardware settings, browser plug-in types and versions; operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create features or promotions; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, or from our Site, including date and time, cookie number, search queries, the phone number from which you called Prep Sportswear, SMS routing information, and your favorite stores. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our Website for fraud prevention and other purposes. We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches. During some customer visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. We may also collect technical information to help us identify your device for fraud prevention and diagnostic purposes. Finally, we may use electronic image requests (also called “web beacons” or “single-pixel gifs”) to count page views and to access cookies. The web beacons do not collect, gather, monitor or share any personal information; rather they are used to compile anonymous information about Site usage.

##### Mobile

When you use a location-enabled device to interact with our services, we may collect and process information about your location and your mobile device, like GPS signals sent by a mobile device or a unique identifier for your device. We may also use various technologies to determine location, such as sensor data from your device that may, for example, provide information on nearby Wi-Fi access points and cell towers. Most mobile devices allow you to disable location services; these controls are typically located in the device’s settings menu. If you have questions about how to disable your device’s location services, we recommend you contact your mobile service carrier or your device manufacturer.

###### What Are Cookies?

Cookies are unique identifiers that we transfer to your device to enable our systems to recognize your device and to provide customized features such as storage of items in your “Cart” between visits to the Site. Cookies also allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. We may use information collected through devices and technologies such as “cookies,” pixel tags, or anonymous identifiers when you interact with the Site or the Site’s features that may appear on other websites. Certain features of our Site are only available through the use of a cookie. Most cookies are “session cookies,” meaning that they are automatically deleted from your device at the end of a session.

##### Can I Avoid Cookies?

You are free to decline our cookies if your browser permits. The “Help” feature on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. You can also disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on’s settings or visiting the Website of its manufacturer. Because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of PrepSportswear.com’s features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Cart or proceed to Checkout, you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently, and you may not be able to use certain features on the Site.

##### Information from Other Sources

We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. For example, we may receive updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties which we use to correct our records.

##### Use of Your Information

By visiting our Site, you agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to enhance our marketing and promotional efforts, to trace and analyze Site usage, to improve our Site content, appearance, utility, and product offerings, to offer you tailored content, to respond to your requests, or to customize our Site content, layout, and services. You agree that we may use your information, such as your e-mail address, to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests, such as administrative notices, product offerings, participation in market research, special discounts or promotions, and communications relevant to your business with Prep Sportswear. Does Prep Sportswear Disclose the Information It Receives? Information about our customers is an important part of our business. We are not in the business of selling any personally identifiable information about you to others. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed. Product Manufacturers and Affiliate Partners Currently, Prep Sportswear manufactures the majority of the products listed on our Site. We may in the future operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with other manufacturers or affiliate partners and may share our data, including personally identifiable information about you, with these manufacturers or affiliate partners when necessary, for example, to complete or ship your order to the correct address.

##### Third-Party Service Providers

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, analyzing or cleaning data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. Such third parties have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but they may not use it for other purposes.

##### Business Transfers

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, websites, subsidiaries, or business units, or be acquired by another company. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets, but usually remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless the customer consents otherwise). We reserve the right to transfer customer information in our possession as part of any such transaction.

##### Legal Disclosure to Protect Prep Sportswear or Others

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with any law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements, including investigation of potential violations; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Prep Sportswear, our users, or others as required or permitted by law. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud detection, security or technical issues, or credit risk reduction. We may disclose information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we believe necessary to comply with an investigation of illegal activity. In addition, it may be necessary to provide certain information about you to collection agencies in the event of non-payment or a payment dispute.

##### Aggregated Information

We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly and with others such as publishers, advertisers or connected sites. For example, we may share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services.

##### International

We process personal information on our servers, which are currently located in the United States, but in the future may also be located in other countries. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live. What Choices Do You Have? You can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of other features on the Site. You can add or update certain information. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those set out in this Privacy Policy.

##### Links to Other Sites

Our Website may contain links to other sites. When you use a link to go from our Site to another website, this Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Prep Sportswear is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site or for the information or content contained in such websites.

##### Minors

Prep Sportswear sells products for use by children, but we sell those products only for purchase by adults. We require children under the age of 13 to inform their parents of their intent to use the Prep Sportswear Site. We also ask that minors under the age of 18 NOT submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor (under the age of 18), you can use our Site only in conjunction with your parent’s or guardian’s permission.

##### Security

We are committed to keeping personal information secure, and we have reasonable technical, administrative and physical safeguards in place to protect personal information from loss, misuse or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card number when confirming an order. We transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. You should protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

##### Accessing and Changing Your Information

Whenever you use Prep Sportswear’s services, we aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is incorrect, we attempt to give you ways to update it or delete it, unless we must keep that information for business or legal purposes. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request. Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so for free, except where it would require a disproportionate effort. We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our Site, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and we may not remove information from our backup systems.

##### Conditions of Use and Updates to Privacy Policy

If you choose to visit Prep Sportswear’s Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the laws of the State of Washington. If you have any concern about privacy by Prep Sportswear, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our business and technology changes constantly, and we reserve the right to make changes to our Site, Privacy Policy or Terms of Use at any time. We will endeavor to make changes by posting them in red-line on these pages for fourteen days and we may e-mail periodic notices about our policies and agreements, but you should also check our Site regularly to see recent changes. Changes addressing new functions for a Service or changes made for legal reasons will be effective immediately. All other changes will not apply retroactively and will become effective fourteen days after they are first posted. If you do not agree to the updated Privacy Policy, you should discontinue your use of the Site and our Service. We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. Your continued use of this Site following posted changes to this Privacy Policy means that you accept those changes.
